Minho Park

Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do, Republic of Korea

☐ +821099689143 • ☑ m.park@kaist.ac.kr • ⑤ pmh9960.github.io

Research Interest

I have a strong interest in the domain of generating synthetic data via generative models. Currently, my research is centered on improving the vision-language models by utilizing large-scale pre-trained models in the data-scarce settings.

Keywords....

- Synthetic data generation with generative models
- Generative models, especially diffusion models
- Data-scarce settings

Education

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Integrated Ph. D. in Artificial Intelligence, GPA: 4.00/4.3

Advisor: Jaegul Choo

Korea University

B.S. in Electrical Engineering, GPA: 4.11/4.5

Gyeonggi Science High School for the Gifted

Daejeon, Republic of Korea Sep. 2021 - Present

Seoul, Republic of Korea *Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021*

Suwon, Republic of Korea

Mar. 2015 - Feb. 2018

Publications

Under review.....

[U2]: **Minho Park**, Sunghyun Park, Jooyeol Yun, and Jaegul Choo. "Unlocking the Potential of Generated Datasets in Name-only Transfer of Vision-Language Models"

[U1]: Jeongho Kim, Gyojung Gu, **Minho Park**, Sunghyun Park, and Jaegul Choo "StableVITON: Learning Semantic Correspondence with Latent Diffusion Model for Virtual Try-On" [Paper] [Code] [Project Page]

Conference Paper.....

[C2]: Minho Park*, Jooyeol Yun*, Seunghwan Choi, and Jaegul Choo. "Learning to Generate Semantic Layouts for Higher Text-Image Correspondence in Text-to-Image Synthesis." *IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2023, Paris, France.* [Paper] [Code] [Project Page]

[C1]: Jooyeol Yun*, Sanghyeon Lee*, Minho Park*, and Jaegul Choo. "iColoriT: Towards Propagating Local Hint to the Right Region in Interactive Colorization by Leveraging Vision Transformer." *IEEE/CVF Winter Conference on Applications of Computer Vision (WACV), 2023, Waikoloa, Hawaii.* [Paper] [Code] [Project Page]

Work Experience

Qualcomm AI Research

Research Intern

O Data generation with generative models

Seoul, Republic of Korea Mar. 2024 - Present

Academic Activities

Conference reviewers: CVPR'24

Talks and Slides.....

- Various Types of Diffusion Models [Slides]
- Segment Anything [Slides]
- Classification with Foundation Models [Slides]
- Consistency Models and BOOT [Slides]
- DDPM [Slides]

Teaching Experience

Al Workshop Instructor....

Deepnoid Tech Meet: Various types of diffusion models, Dec. 2023.

SKT Market Top AI: Segment Anything, Sep. 2023.

YearDream School: Computer Vision, Aug. 2023 - Sep. 2023.

AIGS Symposium: Learning to Generate Semantic Layouts for Higher Text-Image Correspondence in

Text-to-Image Synthesis, Oral session, Aug. 2023.

SKT Market Top AI: Classification with foundation models, *Jul. 2023*.

Samsung-Elice Leader Digital Agility: Tutoring deep learning, Nov. 2022 - Nov. 2022.

Goorm K-Digital Training: Linear Algebra, Nov. 2022 - Nov. 2022.

Teaching Assistant.....

[Al618] Generative and Unsupervised Deep Learning: KAIST, Sep. 2023 - Dec. 2023.

DAVIAN basic study: Linear Algebra, Jul. 2023 - Aug. 2023.

SK ML Engineer Course: Computer Vision, Jun. 2023 - Jul 2023.

DAVIAN basic study: Computer Vision, Jan. 2023 - Feb. 2023.

DAVIAN basic study: Computer Vision, Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022.

Samsung-SNU AI Expert Course: Linear Algebra, May. 2022

Reference

Jaegul Choo

KAIST

Associate Professor jchoo@kaist.ac.kr